



I am a Front End Developer with experience in developing websites. I have 3 years of experience in web development and I am also passionate about UX/UI and web performance. I can utilize my experience and skills to enhance aesthetics and improve user experience. Additionally, I see this as an opportunity to expand my knowledge by taking on new challenges.



03/11/1998



thinhpham67ag@gmail.co

- 223/6 Luong The Vinh street, Pho Que hamlet, My Long ward, Long Xuyen City, An Giang Province
- 0702895474
- 🕠 thinhpham311-dev

# Thinh Pham



# QUÉT MÃ QR





HTML, CSS and Javascript

Reactis and NextJS

Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

WordPress



CHỨNG CHỈ

**B1 ENGLISH** 

03/2019



# **EDUCATION**

05/2017 - 09/2020

### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING** - An Giang University

- Learn more about business analysis and graphic design to apply to web products.
- Learn Software Development Process
- Learn algorithmic programming techniques and algorithms



# CAREER HISTORY



01/2023 - 12/2023

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER - TechVSI Company

- Developed and maintained websites for Singapore customers on the WordPress platform.
- Developed and maintained components and libraries to ensure code reusability in ReactJS, NextJS, Svelte projects.
- Utilized CSS libraries such as Tailwind CSS and SCSS to build and maintain the front-end of web applications and landing page.
- Implemented the integration of REST API and GraphQL, and assisted in integrating third-party APIs for JavaScript framework-based web projects.
- Optimized React performance using techniques such as lazy loading, code splitting, and memoization.

## **WEB DEVELOPER** - Antking Company

- Developed websites for Singapore customers on the WordPress platform
- Optimized application codebase, reducing bugs and improving overall system stability and performance and accessibility.
- Worked closely with backend developers to integrate RESTful APIs, improving data consistency and reliability across the application.
- Implemented a new component-based architecture using React.js and developed new features such as authentication, role-based permissions, and a to-do list for the Sidekick Admin website project.
- Participated in code reviews and pair programming sessions, improving code quality and team collaboration.



### FRONT-END DEVELOPER - PAP Technology company

- Developed the website interface based on the design using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Worked closely with backend developers to integrate RESTful APIs, improving data consistency and reliability across the application.
- Collaborated with UX/UI designers to create intuitive, userfriendly interfaces
- Optimized website's SEO performance, resulting in a 30% increase in organic traffic and increase in overall site visibility on search engines.



#### **CHILD EDUCATION**

05/2023 - 06/2023

Description: Child Ed specialises in the publishing and distribution of educational products and resources in Singapore such as big books, picture books, instructional materials, music and reading programs, videos, etc,...

Link: https://www.childed.com.sg/.

Technology: React, Redux Position: Front End Developer

# Responsibilities:

- Developed a dynamic and user-friendly dashboard interface using React to manage educational products and resources, allowing administrators to easily upload, update, and organize content.
- Implemented Redux for efficient state management across the dashboard, ensuring smooth data flow between components and providing real-time updates for various sections like inventory, orders, and user management.
- Integrated API calls to fetch and display real-time data on the dashboard, such as product listings, sales data, and user activities.
- Implemented secure user authentication and role-based access control for different users (e.g., admin, editor) within the dashboard, ensuring appropriate permissions for each.
- Optimized loading times and performance of the dashboard by using React hooks, lazy loading, and efficient state management techniques.

#### **MAXWELL RESERVE RESTAURANT**

Description: Developed introduce hotel and restaurant chains website Link: https://maxwellreserve.com/, https://officersmesspolobar.sg/, https://shikar.sg/. Technology: Wordpress, Elementor plugin, ACF (Advance Custom Field) and Javascript

Position: WordPress Developer

#### Responsibilities:

- Designed and implemented custom layouts and user interfaces for the hotel and restaurant websites using WordPress and the Elementor plugin.
- Utilized Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) to add and manage dynamic content for custom sections like menus, event details, room descriptions, and more, making the content easily manageable from the WordPress backend.
- Developed interactive features such as sliders, animations, and dynamic content rendering using JavaScript to enhance the user experience on the websites.
- Modified and extended Elementor elements to suit the specific needs of the websites, ensuring seamless integration with the design requirements.
- Optimized website performance, ensuring fast load times and responsive design for both desktop and mobile users.

BADO.VN 02/2021 - 03/2021

Description: Developed BADO product introduction landing page Link: https://bado.vn/ Technology: HTML/CSS/Javascript/.NET Core Position: Front End Developer

#### Responsibilities:

- Collaborated with UX/UI designers to create intuitive, user-friendly interfaces.
- Utilized .NET Core to develop a REST API that includes: getting article lists, retrieving feature packs for BADO products, registering trial users, and logging in users.
- Developed the interface using HTML/CSS/Bootstrap and made API calls with Ajax.
- Optimized the website's SEO performance, resulting in a 30% increase in organic traffic and a 20% increase in overall site visibility on search engines.

#### **PORTFOLIO PROFILE**

fewebdeveloper.vercel.app/

11/2023 - 12/2023

My PortFolio Website: https://phamtrithinh-0702895474-

**Technique Info:** Nextjs, Framer Motion and Tailwind scss